<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>khalil ait nouisse on &gt;_ Khalil - Portfolio &amp; Blog</title>
    <link>http://Khalilstudio.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content in khalil ait nouisse on &gt;_ Khalil - Portfolio &amp; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://Khalilstudio.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://Khalilstudio.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://Khalilstudio.me/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m a passionate builder who learns by breaking complex problems down and rebuilding them better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My focus is on Cloud &amp;amp; Backend Engineering architecting resilient distributed systems with Go, and streamlining infrastructure using Docker and modern DevOps practices. I strive to make software not just functional, but scalable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Offline, I’m an explorer at heart, chasing sunrises and sunsets for perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogs</title>
      <link>http://Khalilstudio.me/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://Khalilstudio.me/blogs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>http://Khalilstudio.me/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://Khalilstudio.me/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can contact me via Email, LinkedIn, Discord or X. I usually respond within a day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>http://Khalilstudio.me/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://Khalilstudio.me/experience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In my experience, I’ve worked on projects at the intersection of AI, Backend Engineering, and System Architecture. I designed the global architecture for a multi-agent system integrated with a CRM application, implementing asynchronous communication with Redis and intelligent workflows using LangGraph. I also contributed to X-GATE, an AI-powered platform for businesses, where I built data ingestion pipelines and RAG workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond development, I focused on infrastructure and reproducibility by setting up full-stack Docker environments and implementing tracing for agent performance. These projects reflect my drive to build scalable, production-ready solutions that bridge the gap between intelligent algorithms and solid engineering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://Khalilstudio.me/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://Khalilstudio.me/projects/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are some of my recent projects that showcase my skills and interests in technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
